[
    {
        "title": "2023"
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Which city held the 2023 Eurovision Song Contest?",
        "answer": "Liverpool"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which two countries hosted the 2023 FIFA Women’s World Cup?",
        "answer": "Australia and New Zealand"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What was the Oxford English Dictionary word of the year in 2023?",
        "answer": "Rizz"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which British TV show celebrated its 60th anniversary in November 2023?",
        "answer": "Dr Who"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Nicola Sturgeon resigned as Scotland’s First Minister in February 2023. How many years was she in office for?",
        "answer": "8 or 9"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "The Beatles released their last song in 2023. What is it called?",
        "answer": "Now and Then"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Which artist performed at the Superbowl half-time show in their first live performance for six years?",
        "answer": "Rihanna"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which film won the Academy Award for best picture in 2023?",
        "answer": "Everything Everywhere All at Once"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "The first female Speaker of the House and MP for West Bromwich died in 2023. What is her name?",
        "answer": "Betty Boothroyd"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "In 2023 which Englishman posed for photographs wearing lederhosen, eating white sausage and drinking beer?",
        "answer": "Harry Kane"
    }
]
